s0ft4pc.com 2019-06-02

# Privacy Policy - S0ft4PC

The following Privacy Policy governs the manner in which the website uses, maintains and discloses information collected from its users. The privacy policy applies to every product and service offered by www.s0ft4pc.com.

**Personal identification information:**  
We may collect personal information from users in a various ways when they visit our website, subscribe to the newsletter and fill out a form in connection with products and services featured on our website. Users may be asked for their name and email address but they also have the option to visit the website anonymously. Therefore, we collect personal identification information from users only if they provide it voluntarily. Users can always refuse to provide personal identification information. However, this may prevent them from using certain features of the website where provision of such information is deemed necessary.

**Non-personal identification information:**  
We may collect non-personal identification information about users which may include the browser name, type of computer, the operating system, Internet service providers and other relevant technical information.

**The use of web browser cookies:**  
Our Site may use “cookies” to enhance user experience and enabling them will provide complete access to every feature of the website. However, it is totally on user discretion to enable this feature or not.

**How do we use collected information?**

“S0ft4PC” may collect and use information as follows:  
• To improve customer service: Collected information helps us in responding to your individual needs more effectively.  
• To personalize user experience: Understand comprehensively how our products and services are being used.  
• To improve our Site: The feedback option helps us in improving our products and services according to changing consumer needs.  
• To send periodic emails: User’s email addresses are only used to respond to inquiries and other requests.

**How do we protect your information?**  
By adopting appropriate data collection, storage and processing methods we ensure security against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure, destruction of your personal information, username, password, transaction information and any other information stored in our website.

Our Site is in compliance with PCI vulnerability standards in order to create a secure environment for our users.

**How do we share your personal information?**  
We do not sell, trade, or rent any information collected. We may share generic aggregated demographic information regarding visitors and users with our business partners, trusted affiliates and advertisers for the purposes outlined above but will not disclose any individual information about any specific user or visitor. We may use third party service providers for operational activities such as sending out newsletters or surveys. We may share information with these third parties provided that you have given us permission to do so.

**Terms and Conditions of the advertisements on our website:**  
Advertisements appearing on our website may use cookies which allow the ad server to recognize your computer. This is used to compile non personal identification information about your usage allowing advertisement networks to execute effective targeted advertisement. This privacy policy does not cover the use of cookies by any of our advertisers.

**Terms and Conditions of Google advertisements:**  
Advertisements served by Google uses DART cookie which only uses non personal identifiable information and cannot track personal information about you e.g. name, email address, physical address, etc. You may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at https://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html

**Terms and Conditions about changes to this privacy policy:**  
“S0ft4PC” has the discretion to update this privacy policy whenever it is needed. However, any update will be notified on our main page and the revision date will also be updated below. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect any personal information. By agreeing to our privacy policy, it is your responsibility to periodically become aware of modifications.

**When do you accept these terms and conditions?**  
By using our website, you provide implicit acceptance of this privacy policy. If you do not agree to any part of this privacy policy, we recommend you not to use any feature of the website.

**Contact us!**  
If you have any queries related to this Privacy Policy, our website and its features please contact us on the following email address:

help@s0ft4pc.com
